Finding Aid for the Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association Records LSC.0874
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Los Liones Acquisition - Mountains Recreation and Conservation Authority
  - Land transfers - Development in Pacific Palisades portion of Santa Monica Mountains. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Proposal for Public Acquisition of Los Liones Canyon., 1974; (2 copies) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Maps., n.d. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Coastal Transportation Corridor Specific Plan - Impacts on Air Quality
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Summary of Draft EIR for the Specific Plan & Related district and community amendments., 1985 March (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Preliminary ordinance., 1985 March (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Coastal Transportation Corridor Specific Plan., 1985 April (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Strikeout Version Coastal Transportation Specific Plan., 1985 July (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1986 January-March (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1986 July-September (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1986 January-March (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1986 April-June (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1985 October-December (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1985 July-September (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data., 1986 October-December (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data - Summary of 1984 air quality data. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data - Summary of 1984 air quality data., 1982 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - California Air Resources Board - California air quality data - Summary of 1984 air quality data., 1983 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Fiscal and economic impacts of the Los Angeles Coastal Transportation Corridor Specific Plan., 1985 April 19 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles City Planning Department - Response to written comments on the Coastal Trans Corr Spec Plan., 1986 December (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles City Planning Department - Consideration of changes to the Proposed Trans Corr Spec Plan., 1985 July (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Existing conditions and projected deficiencies - Issues to be resolved... - Preliminary draft., 1984 September (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Draft EIR for the City of Los Angeles Coastal Trans Corr Spec Plan and related... amendments., 1985 March (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Notes., n.d.; (Spiralbound notebook) (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Water management in San Diego: A view from the end of the tunnel... by Rubell Helgeson., 1987 March (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - An analysis of Los Angeles' new approach to traffic mgmt and infrastructure... by Rubell Helgeson., 1986 April (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Draft reply to City Planning Department response... by Rubell Helgeson., 1987 January (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Summary of analysis... by Rubell Helgeson., 1986 August; (2 copies) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Air quality impacts... by Rubell Helgeson., 1986 June 18; (3 copies) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Air quality impacts.. .:An analysis of future carbon monoxide levels... by Rubell Helgeson., 1986 July; (6 copies + 3 appendices) (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Air quality impacts.. .:An analysis of future carbon monoxide levels... by Rubell Helgeson., 1986 July; (1 copy + additional materials) (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Bibliography., n.d. (Box 54, Folder 9)
- View Point Park
  - 301 Mt Holyoke - Kinsey - Folder., 1990-1997 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - 301 Mt Holyoke - Kinsey - Photographs., 1990-1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - 301 Mt Holyoke - Kinsey - Miscellaneous documents., 1990-1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - 301 Mt Holyoke - Kinsey - Maps., 1990-1997 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Via de las Olas Park - Bernheimer., 1990s (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Via de las Olas Park - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Via de las Olas Park - Photographs., 1990s (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Via de las Olas Park - Maps., 1990s (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Castellamare
  - Sunset - PCH., 1980s & 1990s (Box 56, Folder 4)
- PPRA Newsletter
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s & 1990s (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Bowdoin Street Closure - Miscellaneous PPPOA Issues
  - Women's club., 1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Temescal., 1970s (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Petitions., 1970s (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Women's club., 1970s (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Slides., 1980 November (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Audiotape - SMMC Meeting at Temescal Canyon., 1997 July 14 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s (Box 58, Folder 3-5)
  - 1544 Lachman Lane., 1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents - Notes., 1970s (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Traffic control study., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 2-7)
  - Accidents - Time checks., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Accidents - Newspaper clippings., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Petitions - Support letters., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Condemnations., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Braude survey., 1970s (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Village Specific Plan
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from Marvin Braude., 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings - Palisades., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Height, Bulk & Setback / Views., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Background - General., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Utilities., 1983 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Landscaping / Scenic highway., 1983 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Bike issues., 1983 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Traffic., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Parking., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Street treatments., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - TSP Subcomittee recommends., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Architectural review board - Sign controls., 1980s (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Agendas, minutes, procedures, notice / CAC notes., 1980s (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence., 1980s (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Draft Specific Plan., 1984 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Central city pedestrian survey., 1982 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Maps., 1980s (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Mountains Development - Watt / Lachman - Helgeson - Miscellaneous Issues
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s & 1980s (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
  - TT 40432., 1980s (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Theater letters., 1980s (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Coastal hearing of 21601., 1978 March (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Headlands and AMH EIR., 1980s (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - TT 40432 - Draft EIR., n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Watt / AMH Settlement., 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Lachman golf course - Miscellaneous., 1980s (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
  - Marquez Knolls - Traffic studies., 1970s & 1980s (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Park Acquisition - State Park.. .Campaign Information
  - Cumulative Impacts of Potential Development in the Santa Monica Mountains Coastal Zone., 1979 February (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Home sales - Developer.. .etc. - Newspaper clippings., 1970s (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Santa Monica Mountain Plans - Parks., 1970s (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Politics - Races - Fundraisers., 1981 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Elections., 1982 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Santa Monica Mountains - Articles., 1970s (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Park acquisition - Newspaper clippings., 1970s & 1980s (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Proposed 5th Annual Work Program - Draft - Community Redevelopment Agency - City of Los Angeles., 1981 April (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Environment - General - Endangered species - Newspaper clippings., 1960s & 1970s (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Rules - Regulations - Reganomics - Newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Socioeconomic data - Newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Oil - Minerals - Energy - Utilities - Chemicals., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Banks - Interest rates - etc., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Water - etc., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Corporations - etc., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Land - Land use litigation - etc., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Phase-outs - Nonconforming uses - Substandard lots - Surplus land city., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Publishing - etc., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Housing inventory - Policy., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - James Watt - Miscellaneous documents - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Prop R - Super Scooper Fire Fighting Plane
  - Miscellaneous documents - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - PPPOA - Brush fire safety subcommitte status report., 1980 March; (2 copies) (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Rustic Canyon
  - Storm damage - Newspaper clippings., 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Flood - Newspaper clippings., 1970s & 1980s (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Escondido Canyon - Santa Monica Mountains
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Attorney General Ops., 1993 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Contract., 1994 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Maps - Photographs., 1990s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Access / Management - Correspondence., 1993 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Title policy 1990 - 1st Parcel acquired (Flood property) 1993., 1990 & 1993 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Access / Management - Parcel information / Maps - Freedman parcel., 1993 May (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Land gate., 1990s (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Appraisal - Escondido / Fairfax., 1993 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence re photo albums., 1994 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous newspapers clippings., 1990 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence., 1993. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Flood - Correspondence., 1990s (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - AG's files - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s & 1990s (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Drafts - SMMC - PFP., 1994 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Consultants' names., 1993 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Internal memos - PFP., 1994 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Murphy parcel., 1993 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous documents - Correspondence., 1990s (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - For final report., 1990s (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Response to public comments., 1995 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary draft report economic evaluation of alternative general plans for Santa Monica Mountains., 1978 June (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Cumulative impacts of small lot subdivision developments in the Santa Monica Mountians coastal zone., 1979 January (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Letters of support., 1990s (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - TPL - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Access / Management - Coastal permits., 1994 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Public meeting and final report., 1994 January (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Letters, petitions, stipulations., 1994 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Escondido Canyon: Hidden Jewel of the Santa Monica Mountiains - For People for Parks... by Geo Safety. (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Brentwood Palisades Community Plan
  - Headlands - Bienvenida - Sunset (Slides)., 1978 February (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Scenic highway., 1978 January (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Zoning - Brentwood / Pacific Palisades., 1978 & 1994 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 72, Folder 4-6)
  - Newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Village CAE - Traffic studies., 1984. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Cleanup., 1996 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Workshop questionnaire., 1984 April (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s & 1980s (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Recommendation of Commission Hearing Examiner., 1981 October (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Plan., 1976 March (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Staff Recommendation., 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - EIR - Supplement., 1975 December (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Planning - Majority report., 1970s (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - EIR - Summary., 1975 March (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Asessment for the Preliminary... District Plan., 1974 September (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Flood Plan Management Insurance., 1970s (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Ruling on organization as an "aggrieved person"., 1975 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - EIR Seminar., 1980s (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Pacific legal foundation requirements for regs re interpretive guidelines and policy statements., 1986 March (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Highways - PCH - etc., 1980s (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Draft EIR., 1975 August (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Plan Consitency Changes - Plan amendments., 1985 October (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Transportation Element of General Plan., 1990s (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Maps., 1980s (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Public schools., 1980s (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Implementation., 1970s & 1980s (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Topanga and Will Rogers State Beach Plan., 1986 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Coastal Act Guidelines., 1980 October (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Conservation Guide - Las Virgenes Unified School District., n.d. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Open Space Plan - Department of City Planning., 1973 June (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - EIR for the Brentwood Pacific Palisageds District Plan - Miscellaneous documents., 1975 August & 1977 February (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Public Recreation Plan., 1979 November (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Citywide Plan - Department of City Planning., 1974 April (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Planning Guidelines Landform Grading Manual., 1983 June (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Noise Element - Department of City Planning., 1975 September (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Citizens' Advisory Committee on the Mulholland Scenic Parkway., 1972 September (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Information Paper - Los Angeles City Planning Department., n.d. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Bicycle Plan - a Part of the Circulation Element of the City General Plan - Department of City Planning Los Angeles., 1977 July (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Conservation Plan - Department of City Planning Los Angeles., 1973 December (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Scenic Highways Plan - a Part of the Circulation Element of the General Plan of the City of Los Angeles., 1978 February (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Housing Element - an Element of the General Plan - City of Los Angeles - Department of City Planning., 1979 October (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Environmental data index - Office of Environmental Quality - Department of City Planning Los Angeles., 1978 February (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Concept Los Angeles - The Concept of the Los Angeles General Plan., 1974 April (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Seismic Safety Plan - Department of City Planning Los Angeles., 1975 September (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Los Angeles City Planning., 1971-1981 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Los Angeles City Gevernment., 1971-1981 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Fire Protection and Prevention Plan - a Part of the General Plan - City of Los Angeles., 1979 January (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Safety Plan - an Element of the General Plan of the City of Los Angeles - Department of City Planning Los Angeles., 1975 September (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Land & Water building - Local history., 1980s (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Land & Water building - Newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - First community plan implementation., 1973-1980 (Box 76, Folder 3-5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Revision of the City's Noise Element General Plan., 1998 November (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Staff report to the City Planning Commission - Code Amendment., 1999 December (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Lancer - Waste - Waste Burning - Air Quality
  - Lancer - Air quality - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - The dilemma of municipal solid waste mgmt: an examination of the rise of incineration... UCLA Urban Planning., n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 82, Folder 4-5)
- Area 4 Alternative School - Temescal Canyon
  - YMCA of met Los Angeles vs. Synod of southern CA - Complaint.. .Breach of Contract... - Answer., 1980 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Public hearing on draft EIR re Proposed Area 4 Alternative School site., 1980 July (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Photographs., 1980s (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Appraisal value of Los Angeles Unified School District site in upper Temescal Canyon., 1982 May (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Temescal - Synod Pre-EIR., 1984 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate Temescal Canyon Assoc files., 1970s (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Poster., n.d. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Controller's annual financial report - Los Angeles Unified School District., 1990 June (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 83, Folder 9-11)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Unified School District - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Jr High - Upper Temescal Canyon., 1979 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Archeology - Flora & fauna., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - DWP - Conservancy., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - School closures - Newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Unified School District - Busing., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Crawford vs. Board of Education - Integration issues., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Temescal school - Guidelines., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Temescal school - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Temescal school - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Temescal school - Shards & shells., n.d. (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Temescal school - School board., 1980s (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Alternate sites - Costs., 1980s (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - General file - Miscellaneous documents., 1970s & 1980s (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - General file - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1970s & 1980s (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Quality Board hearings re Temescal., 1979 October (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Temescal history., 1970s & 1980s (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Early City actions on upper Temescal., 1960s & 1970s (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Draft EIR., 1980 June (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Oil
  - Miscellaneous notes., 1980s & 1990s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - No Oil briefs., 1980s (Box 77, Folder 4-5)
  - Oceanwood estates - Case no.C354, 343., 1980s (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - PCH study., 1983 December (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Issues - ZPC Open space., 1990s (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Malibu coastal exclusion bills., 1984 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Review of Geologic Data - Final EIR... - Occidental Palisades Oil Drilling Project., 1982 September (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Port of Los Angeles Proposed Plan - Oil drilling (Rezoning / Recovery)., 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Occidental Oil Report - Draft copy., 1976 October (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Staff rec on coastal permit application - Occidental Petroleum Pacific Palisades Oil & Gas drilling., 1981 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - No Oil vs. Chevron., 1970s & 1980s (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Occidental Petroleum Corporation - Hearing before the Associate Zoning Admin., 1985 August (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Sunset International Petroleum., 1981 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - LRC - Annual report., 1981 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 80, Folder 6-9)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Legal documents., 1985 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - No Oil vs. City of Los Angeles / Occidental Petroleum Corporation - Appeals reversed., 1987 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Tidelands trust issues / Occidental property., 1982 October (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - No Oil vs. City of Los Angeles / Occidental Petroleum Corporation - Petitioners' reply re slope limitations., 1985 December (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence., 1985 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Occidental Petroleum Corporation - Hearing before the associate zoning admin., 1985 August (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Appeal from permit decsion of local government., 1986 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 81, Folder 8-9)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Maps
  - Headlands - TT 31935 - Per coastal (misplaced split rock). (Box 86)
    Containers 86, 87, 88 & 89 are oversize roll containers, stored in Map Room.
  - Los Angeles council district index. (Box 86)
  - Headlands Phases I & II. (Box 86)
  - Two Pacific Coast Highway maps., n.d. (Box 86)
  - Tentative Tract 40432., n.d. (Box 86)
  - Pacific Palisades North Coastal Boundary with Mello amendments - Weswood Basic Index map. (Box 86)
  - Four Palisades highlands maps - Land Use. (Box 87)
  - Headlands permit / Highlands Coastal Exhibit. (Box 87)
  - Temescal., n.d. (Box 87)
  - AMH/Watt - TT 21601., n.d. (Box 87)
  - Gateway - Final Phase II., n.d. (Box 87)
  - 1945 Topo - Temescal - Presbyterian Conference Grounds. (Box 87)
  - Palisades Highlands - Land use. (Box 88)
  - TT 31935., n.d. (Box 88)
  - Palisades Highlands - Gateway - Masterplan. (Box 88)
  - AMH/Watt - TT 21601., n.d. (Box 88)
  - AMH/Watt - TT 30453., n.d. (Box 88)
  - AMH/Watt - TT 40432., n.d. (Box 88)
  - TT 32184., n.d. (Box 88)
  - TT 32184 (hand drawn). (Box 89)
  - Community Plan Master maps., n.d. (Box 89)
  - TT 32824 - Water tank landscape plan. (Box 89)
  - TT 32184 (transparency)., n.d. (Box 89)
  - TT 32184 (transparency)., n.d. (Box 89)
  - TT 32148 (colored)., n.d. (Box 89)
  - TT 32184 - Proposed zoning (transparency)., n.d. (Box 89)
  - Headlands Phase II. (Box 89)
  - TT 32184., n.d. (Box 89)
  - Lachman lane - TT 40432., n.d. (Box 90)
    Containers 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95 & 96 are oversize map folders.
  - Temescal - Temescal Canyon - Sheet 4 of 5., n.d. (Box 90)
  - Temescal - Temescal Canyon Park - Santa Monica Mountains Conservancy Concept Plan., 1984 December 12 (Box 90)
  - Oil - Proposed plan map - Port of Los Angeles., n.d. (Box 90)
  - Lachman lane - Travel time study., n.d. (Box 90)
  - Lachman lane - Pacific Palisades Drive & Sunset., n.d.; (2 maps) (Box 90)
  - Lachman lane - TT 40432 Las Canoas Rd., n.d.; (2 maps) (Box 90)
  - Lachman lane - Route 60 (1) freeway., n.d. (Box 90)
  - Lachman lane - Community plan (hand drawn). (Box 90)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Councilman District 11 (South) - Marvin Braude Councilman., 1978 December 13 (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Plan and height district amendments. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Land use plan Pacific Palisades District. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Proposed plan map., 1976 March 4 (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Zoning redesignations., n.d. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Existing land use. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Zoning redesignations., n.d. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Plan and height district amendments. (Box 91)